Focus to insurance stocks now. General
insurance data for the month of March is
out and it looks like ICICI Lombard has
outperformed its peers with over 20%
growth in its premium. Yash is here with
more details on this. Yash? Well, that's
correct for ICICI Lombard. It's
outperformance certainly as far as the
industry average is concerned and
outperformance by a sizable margin. In
the month of March, the general
insurance data has been announced and
ICICI Lombard has managed to grow its
premium by 21% that is in the month of
March. On the other hand, if this has to
be compared with the industry, the
industry has grown its premium at about
8%. ICICI Lombard's fourth quarter FY26
premium that because of the strong
performance is seen showing a growth of
about 18% versus for the industry in the
fourth quarter of FY26, the premium
growth just stands at about 5%. New
India Assurance, the premium growth is
at 13%. Go Digit General Insurance is at
10%. Both these numbers are for the
month of March. Niva Bupa premium growth
in the month of March stands at 37%.
Compare this to the growth with
standalone health insurance industry is
seen. That stands at 22%. Star Health is
growing at 16% in the month of March
against, as I said, standalone health
insurance industry growing its premium
at 22%.
Yash, thank you for those updates there.
Now, in a boost for